[Music]
two steps for a two ingredients eight or
nine different pills it looks like a lot
of stuff and so there's a question of
what was the basis of coming to the sort
of the determined you just kind of throw
in everything that seemed like it has an
uncommon benefit no it's important to
kind of identified it even just to the
brain in transit and appropriate states
not including soaping smart growth
rather chemical decision or criteria our
initial chemical database that we
started our formulation process with was
over five accounts and many of them we
actually think are great for specific
applications but weren't great for this
particular application for widespread
general well tolerated general cognitive
enhancement states free for you and so
[Music]
why why we have some ingredient is
because there's a lot of companies are
glutamatergic on the acetylcholine
pathway the catecholamine athletes the
HPA axis and adaptogens are necessary
they are the brain nutrients and the
note robux that you know cellular energy
process is affected by ATP mandating and
equals regulation there are a lot of
things that are involved and
meaningful cognitive productivity state
conduction etc and so we're not acting
all that be nearly impossible to do but
we are affecting something like cellular
energy effect on everything as you are
increasing cellular energy that has a
effect across everything themselves too
if you're protecting such as well like
some of the antioxidant from fossils is
it affected cell membranes that just in
basically say to you everything is
happening society a little action in our
body there are some kind of bottom-up
supports of some of the rate limiting
meaningful cellular biologic functions
that have producers kind of connect and
then there are very specific effects of
which are being largely at now chemical
level and if any of those steps will
remove from here the effective us code
so in addition to which ingredients we
chose and the amounts those ingredients
the delivery of those ingredients and
the specific forms and them also very
equals our process and oftentimes that
then significantly increased expense on
our side of the goal in our design
processes was not accurate spent on
which is actually fine senator can there
at work and so we go through this with
every ingredient and on the site whiskey
took any of it with I'm using three
names exactly I mean is involved in
hundreds of mechanical processes circuit
our body heart muscles and bones who are
specifically seeking to affect cognitive
functions that may contain involved in
and so my musings really has is
magnesium bound to treat me you main
considerations magnet about to citric
acid maybe think about too many
different things an axe in
different aspects of body to complete
hanging jhemini has emotion for most
researching out facility across the
blood-brain barrier discipline and
really the only magnet things that we're
aware of it has the land clinical trial
showing increase several levels of
magnification which they increase all of
the functions and ankle surgeon networks
so that's particularly our goal that's
for us that doesn't need that magnesium
citrate is great access points for
natural curly or equal to one Meganium
will have a function so with each of the
amino acids each of them and be nice to
each of the extraction processes on
botanicals the form in all of those
cases is quite specific to our intended
path
[Music]